(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
I AM FUWA!
MOCO-MOCO!
ARE YOU READY?
いくよー！
LET'S GO-!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Koseki Bijou
Shiori Novella
Mori Calliope
Oozora Subaru
Ookami Mio
Aki Rosenthal
Shirakami Fubuki
AZKi
FUWAMOCO!
RUFFIANS!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime Showtime Anytime Bau Bau
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Lifetime Showtime
FUWA! MOCO!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA (Yay!)
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA! MOCO!
I love being tricky
Doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies
Don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime Showtime Anytime Bau Bau
一生涯
For a lifetime
Sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, fur-over glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime Showtime Anytime Bau Bau
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Woooo... BAU! Woooo... BAU!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy days kept sealed away (BAU!)
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz, we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement, dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin', but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって
Always
It's that day!
Today!
Lifetime!
Showtime!
Not tomorrow BAU BAU!
一生涯
A lifetime
Walk with you!
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter
いつだって
Always
It's that day!
Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday! BAU BAU!
Yeah, Yeah,
二人は
The two of us are
Happy fuzzy yappy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU! Everybody BAU BAU!
Hallo hallo BAU BAU! Everybody BAU BAU!
ダメダメノンノン！ Don't touch the ears!
No no, no no! Don't touch the ears!
もふもふノンノン！ Don't touch the tail!
Fluffy fluffy, no no! Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！ フワワだよ！ バウ！
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
フワワじゃないよ！ モココだよ！ バウ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mokoko! BAU!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! BAU!
And together we're... FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい フー、フー！
I want to be with you! Fu-fu!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい フー、フー！
I want to be with you! Fu-fu!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Fuwa fuwa, moco moco, hand in hand with you!
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it, won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい おー！
I want to be with you! Oh!
Lifetime, Showtime, anytime! BAU BAU!
一生涯
A lifetime
Sing with you!
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime, Showtime, anytime! BAU BAU!
And
together
we're
happy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Let's hear you!
Say BAU BAU!
Fuwa!
Moco!
Yeah!
Fuwa!
Moco!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Wuffians! Omae! Bau Bau!
Wuffians! You guys! Bau Bau!
Welcome to our FUWAMOCO wacha wacha
birthday festival 2026!
Bau Bau! Omae!
Bau Bau! You guys!
Thank you so much for coming to
celebrate our birthday with us, Wuffians!
始まりました！ おーい！
We've started! Hey!
今日は生誕ライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you!
Thank you for coming to our birthday live today!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's variety show,
tonight begins...
today we have a big concert! Yeah!
Can you believe it? It's already been three years!
Right! Our third birthday in Hololive English!
But Mokoko-chan, we can't forget that
really important thing, right?
Huh? What?
Introductions!
Ah, yeah! Okay! Bau!
I'm not a chihuahua!
I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa!
I'm Mokoko!
We're Hololive English Advent's
twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together we're... FUWAMOCO! Bau Bau!
Ah, Mokoko!
We have an amazing birthday festival stage here!
Amazing stage! Wuffians!
Look at the stage! It's so big!
It's such a big boost right too...
Ah, Fuwawa? Oh!
Okay, shall we go?
Three, two, one... Bau Bau!
It's so big and wide, too! Yeah!
Thank you Wuffians for being here today!
But, singing and dancing today is
not just going to be us, right?
No! We're also here with some very special guests, too!
今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来てるから、
We have some wonderful guests coming today too,
ぜひ楽しみにしてくださいね！ Yeah!
so please look forward to it! Yeah!
そして、もう一人、謎のゲストさんも？ 誰かな？
And, there's one more, a mysterious guest? I wonder who it is?
Bau Bau! Oh!
But, a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right, something very important... I think you know well, but...
Hashtag!
Yes, the birthday hashtag!
Right up here you can see our birthday hashtag:
#FWMCbday26! That it is!
Please, please post your thoughts, take lots of photos, screenshots...
ぜひハッシュタグで感想呟いてください。写真もね。
Please tweet your thoughts with the hashtag. Photos too.
後でポチしに行くからね。 Bau Bau!
We'll go look at them later. Bau Bau!
We'll check all your thoughts after the show! Bau Bau!
Also...
We're going to be having a special membership-only
concert right after this, so don't miss it, okay?
Yeah! Uh-huh!
最後にはメンゲンのアンコールライブも
Lastly, there will be an encore live
ありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
for members, so please come and see it!
You know, it is a concert after all, right?
So should we get singing a little more?
Yeah! Yeah!
For this next song...
I think we need a special guest for this, right?
Yeah! Okay, let's call her on together!
Mori Calliope!
みなさん！
Everyone!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
Today only, I am also a dog.
Shinigami dog!
Happy birthday FUWAMOCO!
Thank you for inviting me, I'm happy to be here.
What's up Ruffians!
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh?
I do!
Wow, look at this logo. What does it say?
Check it out!
With respect!
But you know, it'd be cute if we matched, right?
But maybe...
What if we just go run and we'll get
Calliope to entertain you for a second.
Yeah, okay!
Entertain them!
You can do it!
They won't bite!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's
super special splits challenge segment!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
できない...！
I can't...!
I'm sorry, I can't. I can't do it!
I did my best.
Safe, safe! Safe!
But I can, I can still dance.
That's right!
We're matching!
Matching!
Tripleting!
As a nice ring to it.
Has a nice ring to it.
This next song is one that FUWAMOCO
wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Something nostalgic, and I think
you'll be able to see why.
There's some rap in there as well!
But it's also very cute, right?
次に歌う曲は、カリ先輩と一緒に
The next song is one I've always
ずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！
wanted to sing with Calli-senpai!
So true!
It's both cute, it's cool!
But I think, you know, it has an important part that,
you know, you should be proud of what you like, right?
Important meaning of being proud,
being strong about what you like, yeah!
Your likes!
Whether it be games...
Anime...
Idol...
Idols...
Figure!
Figures!
Or maybe even Vtubers!
Nice, keep it missing there.
After all, life is more fun when
you're just true to yourself, right?
Definitely!
I agree!
So we're going to sing this song for you, okay?
Okay, let's do the title call together, okay?
Yes!
聴いてください！
Listen to it!
Like! Like! Like!
My trio be fun
We run
Like! Like! Like!
My trio be fun
We run
Like! Like! Like!
My trio be fun
We run
Comic, I like it!
Music, I like it!
Game, I like it!
Animation, I like it!
Figure, I like it!
Movie, I like it!
Wonder, I like it!
Hobby, I like it!
Go go go go go go go go!
You like it?
I like it!
Go go go go go go go go!
You like it?
I like it!
人生楽しんだもん勝ち 驚きさ アンニョン
Those who enjoy life win, Surprising, Hello
好きなもの好きって言えたらそれスーパーノヴァ
If you can say you like what you like, that's a Supernova
快感超絶マックス登らさ アンニョン
Pleasure transcendental max climb, Hello
丸裸きな裸足 駆け出そうよ 煩悩丸
Completely naked barefoot, Let's run out, Bundle of worldly desires
マジック マジック マウイ 駆動で ごめん
Magic magic Maui, Sorry for driving
キープした軸は 一生でしょう
The axis kept will be for a lifetime, right?
今すぐ Let's make sound
Right now, Let's make sound
君が部屋にいたって メンクスすれば コンサート
Even if you're in your room, if you 'menks' it's a concert
いつだってお目目ロンリーロンリー ずっと伸ばせ 1, 2
Always eyes lonely lonely, Keep reaching out 1, 2
I like it! I like it!
好きになれば
If you fall in love
きっと全てがカラフルで
I'm sure everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky!
星屑さえ
Even the stardust
光る宝物さ
Will be a shining treasure
I like it! I like it!
君に会えた
I met you
やっと今日からヨロシクね
Finally, from today, nice to meet you
ほら キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling, like a dream
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hold you soon
あれもこれも欲しくて
I want this and that
神様に祈ってる
I'm praying to God
好きでしょうがない
I can't help but love you
次はなににしようかな
I wonder what I should do next
歩く わるない 解く 丸い ほとばす 言葉 Like! Like! Like!
Walking, not bad, solving, round, gushing words Like! Like! Like!
360度パノラマ全方向大好きの陣
360-degree panorama, all-direction 'I love you' formation
何がひとつでもいいから のめりこめる自分のアイテム
If there's even one thing, an item of my own I can get absorbed in
Like a Superstar Fireman 無敵キャンディ 他大概来世
Like a superstar fireman, invincible candy, the rest mostly in the next life
望んでる彼もきっと 現世がいとおしくなるはずなのさ
Even the guy I'm wishing for surely will find this world precious
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
It's not something you try to be, let's just enjoy life and walk along
自分に素直であれ スポットライト 僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, spotlight, shine on us
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ Get down! 旋律のSong for you
I'll just shout my love again today Get down! A melodic song for you
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
Surely everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream-like story
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
ずっと離さないでいてね
Please don't ever let me go
ほらキラキラ虹みたい 世界はまわりだす
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow, the world starts to turn
Ready? Set! Bau Bau Go!
Get her! Get her! Get her!
No! Fuwa-chan! Moco-chan! Power!
好き好き好きでしょう大回転 手に入れたいこの感情
Love, love, love it, right? Great rotation, this feeling I want to obtain
歯止めとサイド 真剣勝負
Brakes and side, a serious match
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ？
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう 恋も悶々事件
Yes, love is also a fretting incident
でもそれが僕の等身大
But that's my true self
キャッシュ飛ばして世界を革命
Blowing off the cache, revolutionizing the world
いわゆるひとつの萌要素
What you'd call a moe element
素直になれたなら Happy days
If I could be honest with myself, happy days
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If I fall in love
きっと全てがカラフルで
Surely everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ 光る宝物さ
Lucky! Lucky! Even the stardust is a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
やっと今日からよろしくね
Finally, from today on, let's be together
ほらキラキラ夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, it's sparkling like a dream, I want to hold you soon
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
Surely everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream-like story
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I was able to meet you
ずっと離さないでいてね
Please don't ever let me go
ほらキラキラ虹みたい 世界はまわりだす
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow, the world starts to turn
That was so fun!
I Like Fuwamoco!
Yeah, yeah!
Bye-bye Bau Bau! Bye-bye!
Please listen to our next song, Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime!
Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime
Lyrics: Tommy february6
Music: MALIBU CONVERTIBLE
街角にならぶ
Lined up on the street corner
映画のポスター
Movie posters
もうこの街にも 明日は
In this city, too, tomorrow...
ドアの向こう側に
Behind the door
溜息を返す
I let out a sigh
キャンセルしないで
Please don't cancel it
Mon amour pour toi
My love for you
ハートの端っこに
In the corner of my heart
隠した写真
A hidden photo
誰も知らない
No one knows
本気の恋
This serious love
神様は気づいてる
God has noticed
Jo t'aime Jo t'aime
Je t'aime, Je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて 見たくないわ
I don't want to see a dream that won't come true
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up
“愛してるわ”
“I love you”
クレープに描く
I draw on a crepe
愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the unending rain
Jo t'aime Jo t'aime
Je t'aime, Je t'aime
こんなあっけない夜に
On such a fleeting night
したくはないから
I don't want to leave it like this
ほんの5分でも
Even if just for 5 minutes
会いたい
I want to see you
キャンディ・ショップも
The candy shop
レコード・ショップも
And the record shop too
あなたがいないと
Without you
つまらない
They're boring
ジャケットのポケットに
With the coin I left
入れたままのコインに
In my jacket pocket
賭けるわ　恋の行方
I'll bet on the outcome of our love
神様が知っている
Only God knows
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
退屈な恋なんて
I don't want
したくないわ
A boring love
あっという間に溺れてく
Drowning in it in the blink of an eye
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before the cafe au lait
しまうその前に
Gets cold
もういちどKISSして
Kiss me one more time
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Lock the story away
Doux Je t'aime
あなたの言葉ばかりを
I'm only dreaming
夢見ている
Of your words
MON AMOUR...
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて
I don't want to see
見たくないわ
A dream that won't come true
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up
“愛してるわ”
"I love you"
クレープに描く
Under the umbrella of love
愛の傘の下で
Drawn on the crepe
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the rain that won't stop
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
MON AMOUR POUR TOI
退屈な恋なんて
I don't want
したくないわ
A boring love
あっという間に溺れてく
Drowning in it in the blink of an eye
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before the cafe au lait
しまうその前に
Gets cold
もういちど聞かせて
Let me hear it once more
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
La la la...
Bau bau!
Wow! Look at this sunset!
It's so exciting already, huh?
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was "Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime."
What did you think, Ruffians?
What'd you think, Ruffians?
It's a little bit more nostalgic?
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
You know, some city pop vibes too!
And the choreography's cute too, right?
Well, we hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy, Ruffians!
Wow, you know, with the sun setting now...
...it's starting to feel a bit romantic almost, right?
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call out my next guest!
Yeah! Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! Aki Rose-senpai!
Bau bau!
Thank you for coming!
Happy Birthday!
嬉しい！ Bau bau!
We're so happy! Bau bau!
おめでとう！ Bau bau!
Congratulations! Bau bau!
あ、自己紹介お願いします。
Ah, please introduce yourselves.
お願いします！
Please!
はい！こんこんこんあずき！AZKiでーす！
Hi! Kon-kon-kon AZKi! I'm AZKi!
はい！ホロライブ1期生、アキ・ローゼンタールことアキロゼでーす！ヤッホロー！
Hi! Hololive 1st Gen, Rosenthal Aki Rose, also known as Aki Rose! Yaholove!
Bau bau! Bau bau!
嬉しい！先輩たち、ありがとうございます！
We're so happy! Senpais, thank you so much!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
このステージで！
On this stage!
このステージで！ Thank you!
On this stage! Thank you!
すごい嬉しい！ あの...
We're so happy! Um...
AZKi先輩とアキロゼ先輩の...
...AZKi-senpai and Aki Rose-senpai's...
歌声がすごく大好きなので！
...singing voices, we love them so much!
えー！すごい！ありがとう！
Eh-! Wow! Thank you!
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
次は曲があって...
Next we have a song...
そう、はい。えっと、まぁ...
That's right, yes. Well, then...
アキロゼ先輩とあずき先輩はとっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので...
Akirose-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such charming big sisters,
あら！
Oh!
そうですか？
Is that so?
...ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました。
...so I thought we'd go with this song.
あらあら。
My my.
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし。
The sun is setting, too.
確かに、ちょっと夕方...
True, it's getting a bit late...
ちょっとロマンチックになりました。
It's gotten a bit romantic.
おお。
Oh.
実はちょっぴりセクシーかも。
Actually, it might be a little sexy.
お、セクシーかも？
Oh, sexy?
セクシーな曲？
A sexy song?
おお！
Oh!
お願いしたいことある？
Is there something we want to ask?
お願いしたいことあるんですけどいいですか？
There's something we'd like to ask, is that okay?
なになに？
What is it?
アキロゼ先輩...
Akirose-senpai...
えっと、この曲を歌う前に少しあのセクシーなウォーミングアップ...
Um, before we sing this song, could we have a little sexy warm-up...
おお！セクシーなウォーミングアップ？
Oh! A sexy warm-up?
教えてもらってもいいですか？
Could you teach us?
セクシーウォーミングアップ、オッケー！
Sexy warm-up, OK!
やったー！オッケー！
Yay! OK!
じゃあ、まずセクシーな体を作るために...
Alright, first, to build a sexy body...
自分の体を...
Your own body...
撫でて。
Caress it.
撫でて？
Caress?
撫でて撫でて。頭撫でて...
Caress, caress. Caress your head...
足から。
From your legs.
足から！セクシー！
From the legs! Sexy!
撫でる。
Caress.
撫でてみて。
Try caressing.
恥ずかしい...
I'm embarrassed...
撫でて... アキロゼ先輩みたいに。
Caress... like Akirose-senpai.
あ、モコちゃんいいよ。
Ah, Moco-chan, that's good.
オッケー、いいよ、いいよ。
Okay, good, good.
いけそう。
I think I've got it.
可愛いよ、可愛いよ。
You're cute, you're cute.
セクシー。撫でるのがセクシー。
Sexy. Caressing is sexy.
セクシーすぎる！
Too sexy!
オーイェー！
Oh yeah!
モコちゃんもう一回、もう一回。
Moco-chan, one more time, one more time.
ちょっと違うかな。
Is that a bit different?
あずきちゃんもなんかセクシーだけど可愛い。
AZKi-chan is also kind of sexy but cute.
そう思いました？
Did you think so?
やっぱこうやって...
After all, like this...
おお、お尻とか。
Oh, your hips and stuff.
いい、いい！
Good, good!
あらあら。
My my.
おしりフリフリ。
Wiggle your hips.
あ、尻尾。
Ah, the tail.
尻尾フリフリも。
Tail wiggles, too.
モコちゃん尻尾フリフリ。
Moco-chan's tail wiggles.
ウォームアップ、ウォームアップ。
Warm-up, warm-up.
オッケーオッケー。
Okay, okay.
いいんじゃない？
Isn't it good?
いいよいいよ。
It's good, it's good.
準備できた。
Preparation complete.
バッチリできた。
Perfectly done.
じゃあ、いい感じになりましたね。
Alright, we're in a good place now.
はい、次の曲行きましょうか。
Yes, shall we go to the next song?
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、聞いてください。
Now, please listen.
「DISCOTHEQUE」！
DISCOTHEQUE!
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PPA
DISCOTHEQUE / Lyrics: 岩里祐穂 / Music: 上松範康 (Elements Garden)
DISCOTHEQUE / Lyrics: Sayuri Iwazato / Music: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN', let's dance
弾ける BEAUTY LADY
Sparkling BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと 彩りたいの
I want to color it gently
潤んだ瞳 唇
Moist eyes and lips
ピンク色の 艶めくネイル
Pink, glossy nails
ガラスの向こう側に
On the other side of the glass
映る素顔 シュールなドレス
My real face reflected, a surreal dress
君だけに そう 見せていたい
I want to show only you, yes
心の中 瞳の奥
Inside my heart, deep in my eyes
側にいてほしいよ
I want you by my side
月のミラーボール 照らされて
Illuminated by the moon's disco ball
MY DARLIN' ねえ ヴィヴィッドな
MY DARLIN', hey, let's have a vivid...
恋しましょう 弾ける SEXY BEAUTY
...love, sparkling SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと 彩る MY LOVE
Gently coloring MY LOVE
ほら 世界は変わる
Look, the world is changing
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PPA
ドラマティックな 事情に
In a dramatic situation
焦せないで デジャブ 満ちていきたくて
Don't rush me, I want to be filled with deja vu
カラフルな ナイスストーリー
A colorful nice story
心 深く 刻み込む
Carving it deep into my heart
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant a spell of love
きっと 果てない空
Surely the endless sky
星屑のシャワー 降り注ぐ
Will be showered with stardust
だから HAPPY STATION
So, let's aim for the...
目指してゆこう 50/50 合わせて
...HAPPY STATION, merging 50/50
100%以上の愛
More than 100% love
揺るぎないココにあると
Being here, unwavering...
私を思ってる
...you think of me
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PPA
Blah-Blah Shibu-Do-Ba...
Go-Sa-Ga-Chi Blah-Ju-Bu
君に ありのまま 好きでいてほしいと
I want you to like me just as I am
願いは
My wish is
素敵な
wonderful
MY DARLING もっと一緒に踊りましょう
MY DARLING, let's dance together more
SECRET NIGHT 素敵な
SECRET NIGHT, a wonderful
へそ出しのデコレイション
navel-showing decoration
二人のハート DE EYE
our two hearts' EYE
重なり合わせて
overlapping each other
MY DARLING ねえ MY DARLING な恋しましょう
MY DARLING, hey, let's have a MY DARLING-like love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
bursting SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって甘い夢
reborn, a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE
gently coloring MY LOVE
ほら
Look,
世界は変わる
the world is changing
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
燃え尽きるわ この恋多分
I'll probably burn out in this love
どんな終幕が来ようと
No matter what kind of ending comes
覚悟してる
I'm prepared
余裕なんて ほとんどない
There's almost no room to breathe
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on
あなたの目 優しく抱き寄せる腕
Your eyes, the arms that gently embrace me
全てが全てが初めてなの
Everything, everything is for the first time
I'm falling in love at the world
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let go
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just as it is
この不安も拭いとって ねえ
Wipe away this anxiety too, hey
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Touch me その指先
Touch me, those fingertips
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me, with that look
この私を包み込んで please
Please, wrap me up
please please please please please please please please
愛してる
I love you
甦るわ きのうのこと
I remember what happened yesterday
あんなに心が揺れたの
My heart shook like that...
初めてだもん
...for the first time
寂しすぎて 時々恐い
It's so lonely it's scary at times
二人でいれない この時が
This time when the two of us can't be together
雨の朝 温かな部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room
大人のふりから
From acting like an adult
本当の大人になりそう
it seems I'm becoming a real adult
Kiss me 危険なほど
Kiss me, to the point of danger
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss
この願いを全部叶えて ねえ
Hey, grant all these wishes
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Knock me その眩しさで
Knock me, with that radiance
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window
この私を安心させて please
Please, reassure me
please please please please please please please please
愛してる
I love you
Kiss me
いけないほど
So much it's wrong
Kiss me
甘いくちづけ
With a sweet kiss
こんな願いを 全部叶えて
Make all these wishes of mine come true
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Knock me その魂で
Knock me with that soul of yours
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window
この私を安心させて Please
Please put my mind at ease
Please Please Please Please Please Please Please Please
愛してる
I love you
BAU BAU!
Are you ready?
Let's do it!
Please enjoy Triangle Dreamer!
Day by day 日々に日々に募る乙女心
Day by day, day by day, a maiden's heart grows fonder
同じクラス斜め前の新しい人
A new person sitting diagonally in front of me in class
かっこよくはないだけど優しい
He's not cool, but he is kind
いつも頼れる彼
He's someone I can always rely on
放課後挨拶だの帰り道
Exchanging greetings after school on the way home
何だって話せる親友の女の子
A best friend girl I can talk to about anything
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて
She's good at sports and studying too
女子力マックスです
She's got maximum feminine charm
どこにでもあるよくあること
It's a common story that could happen anywhere
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she said to me...
「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの」って
"You know, I actually have someone I like."
ちょ マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Love triangle, a love triangle's romance is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses in an instant
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A cliché manga-like flag
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて残念すぎます
I can't believe I'm the one who triggered it, how disappointing
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Love triangle, a love triangle's romance is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that doesn't end with a "Just kidding!"
恋と友情ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship wavering back and forth
なんか青春しちゃいます
I'm having a bit of a youth moment
わたし 困っちゃいます
It's putting me in a tough spot
乾杯です鬼相性すぎるわ勝てっこない
I give up, they're too compatible, I stand no chance
悔しいけどどこかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's frustrating, but I truly mean it
ていうか既に応援モード
In fact, I'm already in support mode
むしろ清々しい
It's actually quite refreshing
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she has a puzzled look on her face
真剣な目で「そうじゃなくて私、あなたがすき ごめん」って
With serious eyes, she said "No, I like you. I'm sorry."
ど マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Love triangle, a love triangle's romance is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses in an instant
わたし アナタ 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her and me
超絶！複雑 百合展開は想定外です！
Super complex! A Yuri development was totally unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Love triangle, a love triangle's romance is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that doesn't end with a "Just kidding!"
解けないパズル与えたもうた
You gave me an unsolvable puzzle
神よ恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I'm starting to resent you
私 悩んじゃいます
I'm starting to worry...
あーもうすごいヤバい！
Ah, geez! This is seriously bad!
好きだよ！
I like you!
あ、好きだけど、
Ah, I mean I do like you,
ってそういう意味じゃなくって！
but not in that way!
だって女の子同士だし！
Because we're both girls!
ねえ神様、
Hey God,
どうしたらいいの？
what should I do?
私、
Me,
どうしたいの？
what do I want to do?
ヘルプミー！
Help me!
なんか変だ 愛に故郷も 年も性別も関係ない
Something's strange—hometown, age,
or gender don't matter in love.
けど けど けど
But, but, but...
三角形 三角形の 恋はきまぐれ
A triangle, a triangle love is fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で くずれるバランス
In an instant, in an instant,
the balance collapses.
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
Even though I dreamed of a normal love.
ノーマル設定の わたしじゃちょっと 無理ゲーすぎます
With my 'normal' settings,
it's just too much of a 'trash game.'
三角形 三角形の 恋は不安定
A triangle, a triangle love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that 'just kidding'
won't settle.
彼女のこと 好きになれたらな
If only I could fall in love with her...
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I find myself daydreaming.
わたし どうかしてます
There's something wrong with me.
いくよー！
Here we go!
はい！
Hai!
ほーい！
Hoey!
わおー！
Waoo!
Wow, Bau Bau!
Thank you Ruffians!
That was so much fun!
Yeah, I know, I got a bit dizzy though...
by the bubble and then changing so quickly!
Oh, nice and fast.
Yeah, you know, just the bubble there was a little bit silly.
Yeah, you know, just the bubble there
was a little bit silly.
But, did we surprise you?
And we got to see you as well, even more close up than usual.
And we got to see you as well,
even more close up than usual.
Oh yeah!
Wow!
Those last two songs we sang were 'Kiss Me I'll Stay Together' with Ahoy-tan...
Those last two songs we sang were
'Kiss Me I'll Stay Together' with Ahoy-tan...
...and 'Triangle Dreamer'!
With Miko-senpai, Marine-senpai, and Subaru-senpai.
With Miko-senpai, Marine-senpai,
and Subaru-senpai.
What'd you think, Ruffians?
'Kiss Me I'll Stay Together' is a song that I've always wanted to sing together with Ahoy-tan.
'Kiss Me I'll Stay Together' is a song
that I've always wanted to sing together
with Ahoy-tan.
It's a little bit more sexy, a bit of a sexy song, huh?
It's a little bit more sexy,
a bit of a sexy song, huh?
Yeah, and 'Triangle Dreamer'! The best-of-all idol song!
Yeah, and 'Triangle Dreamer'!
The best-of-all idol song!
そう、ゆり展開が尊すぎて、え、ラフィアンズ、まだ生きてる？
Right, the yuri developments were so precious...
Wait, Ruffians, are you still alive?
え、生きてる？
Eh, are you alive?
Yeah, Bau Bau!
All our senpais were so cute! In love!
And crowd surfing on the bubble!
Yeah!
It was a blast, a lot of firsts this year, right?
Well, we have a tiny, tiny announcement!
Huh? You know, it's FuwaMoco, it's our birthday, right?
Huh? You know, it's FuwaMoco,
it's our birthday, right?
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you.
And so, we have something we'd like to
share with you.
Okay! Ready? Don-doko-don!
BAU BAU!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with our FuwaMoco 2026 Birthday Merch!
It's time to celebrate both of
our birthdays with our FuwaMoco 2026
Birthday Merch!
フワモコの生誕グッズ紹介、始まるよー！
Introducing the FuwaMoco birthday goods!
Here we go!
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols with the Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa...
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols
with the Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa...
...and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands, drawn by our Mama, Icomochi-mama!
...and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands,
drawn by our Mama, Icomochi-mama!
They're rather big compared to regular acrylic stands, so we think they'd be a great addition to your collection!
They're rather big compared to regular
acrylic stands, so we think they'd be a
great addition to your collection!
大きめサイズの、可愛いアイドルのフワモコアクリルスタンド！
Large-sized, cute idol FuwaMoco
acrylic stands!
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel and Hoeh?! Devil rubber figurines.
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel
and Hoeh?! Devil rubber figurines.
Win-out palm-sized figures perfect for displaying on your desk!
Win-out palm-sized figures perfect for
displaying on your desk!
ハロウィン衣装のフワモコが、手のひらサイズのラバーマスコットになったよ！
FuwaMoco in their Halloween outfits
are now palm-sized rubber mascots!
This one is big!
We finally have FuwaMoco plushies in our Out-and-About casual outfits!
We finally have FuwaMoco plushies
in our Out-and-About casual outfits!
But this time, we also speak when you house us!
But this time, we also speak when
you house us!
It's the Yappy Puppy FuwaMoco Sounds Plushies!
It's the Yappy Puppy FuwaMoco
Sounds Plushies!
We'll be the same size as our Friends with You plushies, so you can display them together!
We'll be the same size as our Friends with You
plushies, so you can display them together!
おしゃべりパピーMOCOCOぬいぐるみのフワモコだよ！ギュッとすると、色々喋るよ。
FUWAMOCO here for the Talking Puppy MOCOCO plushie! If you give it a squeeze, it says all kinds of things.
どんなボイスが出るかお楽しみに！
Look forward to seeing what kind of voices come out!
We have the FUWAMOCO to GO☆Finger Puppet!
おおー！
Ooh!
They both come with one extra Ruffians kigurumi costume you can dress them up in and bring around with you everywhere!
フワモコの指パペット！
FUWAMOCO Finger Puppets!
どこでも一緒に連れて行けるサイズで、着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もありよ！
A size you can take anywhere, and it comes with a Ruffians dress-up costume!
Finally, we have two different ASMR Voice Packs:
"Back from a Fluffy Date♡" with Fuwawa...
...and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo!
ASMRボイスは英語と日本語両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
They make our hearts beat so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them! ううー！
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them! Ugh!
The merch is separated into two sets: Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch.
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses, including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはフワワセットとモココセットに分かれています。
The merch is divided into a Fuwawa set and a Mococo set.
セットごとにチェキ風カードと特典ボイスがつきます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card and bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン入りだよ！
The limited edition set includes a handwritten signature!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさん愛情込めてサイン書きますね！
I'll put a lot of love into writing the signatures!
Please check out the hololive official online shop and look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひ、ホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！
Please check out the hololive official shop!
BAU BAU!
What did you think? About our birthday merch? Pretty cute, huh?
Well, the reservations will be going on sale right after the birthday live here ends. So don't forget, okay?
そう！生誕のグッズの予約はこの後開始しますので、お忘れずにチェックしてください！
That's right! Pre-orders for the birthday merch will start after this, so don't forget to check it out!
Yeah, because the link below or on the side here, BAU BAU! Don't forget, okay?
Mm, we put a lot of love into it and ikomochi-mama! Thank you, ikomochi-mama!
Right after this ends, time to go-go-go!
Yeah, go buy it!
Well, we performed more special collab songs with our dear Senpais...
...but there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
そう、まだ会ってない謎のゲストが一人いるんだよ！
Right, there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
BAU BAU! Well, shall we give the Ruffians a hint?
Ruffians, are you curious?
HOKKOROPY...
YAGO-san...
Ah, YAGO-san?
That's a good guess, maybe!
Well, we'll see, huh?
Maybe you should get ready...
...because, you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero...
...but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Mococo-chan, you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Well, let's get them out here then!
Who could it be, who could it be?
Okay! Se-no... DOUZO!
Okay! Ready, set... GO!
ワワワワ〜！来たしんよ、来たしんよ！来たしんよ〜！
Wa-wa-wa-wa! I'm here, I'm here! I'm here!
BAU BAU! 自己紹介お願いします！
BAU BAU! Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんでーす！ワワワワ〜！
It's Kuro-chan! Wa-wa-wa-wa!
出たしんよー！
I've arrived!
初めまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
二人合わせて、フワモコです！
Together, we are FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
よろしくお願いします！
Please be kind to us!
フワモコのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to FUWAMOCO's wacha wacha Birthday Festival!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ、フワモコ！良いしんね！
Happy Birthday, FUWAMOCO! It's so good!
ありがとう！あ、ちょっとね、視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど...
Thank you! Ah, well, I think there are many Ruffians watching, but...
クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
Could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
自分で！？
By myself!?
そう！イントロダクション！
Yes! An introduction!
分かったしんよ。だってこれ、海外の人も見てますもんね。
I understand. Since overseas people are also watching, right?
海外の人もわかる自己紹介しますからね。
I'll do an introduction that overseas people can understand too.
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you... chu, chu, chu, chu, TULIP!
あ、お... え、困らないで！え、クロちゃんは...チューリップ？
Ah, oh... Eh, don't be troubled! Is Kuro-chan... a tulip?
いや、チューリップ、No, no, no, no!
No, tulip, No, no, no, no!
ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから...
Maybe it's still hard to tell...
えーとね、安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる芸人さんで...
Well, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus...
あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってて、作詞とかもしています、クロちゃんです！
I'm also the producer of Mameshiba no Taigun and write lyrics too, I'm Kuro-chan!
BAU BAU!
じゃあ、今度は英語でお願いします！
Then, this time in English please!
僕が！？自分で！？ Yes!
Me!? By myself!? Yes!
えー、そんなこと急に言われたら...
Eh, if you say that so suddenly...
It's shine! Flower!
言い訳は無し！
No excuses!
ねえ、聞いてる人の話？
Hey, are you listening to what people say?
ねえ。
Hey.
頑張って。よし。
Good luck. All right.
ねえ。いや、英語、えっと、なんだろう、えっと、Famous comedian.
Hey. No, English... uh, what is it... um, Famous comedian.
おお！
Oh!
Comedian.
あと、Idol producer.
Also, Idol producer.
やったー、すごーい！
Hooray, that's amazing!
やってるしんよ。
I'm doing it!
おお、できるしん。
Oh, you can do it!
いいねー。
Nice.
クロちゃんテレビでよく見てるけど、
Kuro-chan, I see you on TV a lot, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと、えっと、ちょっと似てるところが
You have a lot in common with FuwaMoco's pet, Pero-chan...
たくさんあるね。
You have a lot in common.
お、お、本当だ。
Oh, you're right.
え、ちょっと後ろの飾り見てください。見えますか？
Look at the decorations in the back. Can you see them?
おおー。
Oh!
そうするとペロです。
Then it's Pero.
ペロ！
Pero!
ちょっ、待って。球体というか丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait. Isn't it just that we're both spherical/round?
そうじゃない。
It's not that.
本当？
Really?
えっと、クロちゃんと似てるところは、
Um, the things you have in common with Kuro-chan are:
嘘つきで、
Being a liar,
女の子好きで、
Liking girls,
やらしく、うん。
Being perverted, yeah.
だからね、見た目で騙されないで。
So, don't be fooled by appearances.
クロちゃんはそんなんで大丈夫なの？言われて。
Kuro-chan, are you okay being told that?
いや、ひどい。悲しくなってきた。
No, that's cruel. I'm getting sad.
えーんえーんえーん。えーんぽこえんふん。
*Crying sounds*
ええー。
Eeeh.
全然人のギャグを聞かないよね、君たちは。
You guys don't listen to other people's gags at all.
ええー。
Eeeh.
できればクロちゃんはペロの友達になってくれませんか？
If possible, Kuro-chan, won't you become Pero's friend?
フワモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達になるの？
Not FuwaMoco's friend, but Pero's friend?
フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから。
Because FuwaMoco doesn't want to be friends with you.
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that strange?
いやいや、気持ち悪いから。
No, no, because it's gross.
いや、気持ち悪くない。マニアには受ける。
No, it's not gross. Geeks like it.
いや、違う。フワ、気持ち悪い、やっぱり。
No, way. It's gross after all, Fuwa.
でもモコちゃん、はい、ちょっとやりすぎですよ。失礼です。
But Mococo-chan, you're going a bit too far. It's rude.
失礼です。
It's rude.
いや、もしもし、ペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら、クロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだほうがいいんじゃない？
If you want me to get along with Pero, shouldn't you ask Kuro-chan nicely?
はあ？
Huh?
ノー。
No.
え、ノー。
Eh, no.
ノー。
No.
しっかりとした否定。
A firm denial.
ノー。
No.
ま、けどペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいと思ってるよ。
Well, but Pero is cute, so I think it's okay for us to get along.
あ、嬉しい嬉しい嬉しい。
Oh, happy, happy, happy.
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな。
He's not cute, but I'd be happy if you got along.
感情が、感情が色々ありすぎるのよ、本当に。
There are just too many different emotions, really.
はい。
Yes.
まあまあ。クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね。ね。
Anyway. Kuro-chan, you're a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
そう。元々アイドルを目指してたのに騙されて芸人にされたから、アイドルは夢、ドリーム。
Right. I wanted to be an idol but was tricked into comedy, so it's my dream.
ああ、なんか悲しいな。可哀想。
Ah, that's kind of sad. Poor thing.
でもドリームって大事ですから。大事。うん。
But dreams are important. Important. Yeah.
さ、で、ま、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、
So, since your dream is to be an idol,
もうせっかく一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
why don't you sing with us?
ああ。
Ah.
いいしんよ、いいしんよ。オッケーだしんよ。
I'd love to! It's totally okay!
オッケー。
Okay.
え、この曲を踊るの？
Eh, you're going to dance to this song?
あの、ハードル上げないで。
Um, don't raise the bar too high.
大丈夫でしょ。アイドルプロデュースもやってるし。
It'll be fine. You're an idol producer too.
そうそう。実力見せてよ。
Yeah. Show us your skills.
見せて！
Show us!
オッケーだしんよ。行くしんよ、行くしんよ。
Okay! Let's go, let's go!
オッケー。
Okay.
じゃ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう。
Then, let's sing a very cute song together.
何歌うんだ？楽しみ。
What are we singing? I'm looking forward to it.
オッケー。
Okay.
はい。
Yes.
じゃ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね。ね。
Then, let's say the title together. Ready?
ほう。
Oh.
せーの。ちゅ、多様性。
One, two... Chu, Tayousei.
あ、多様性やるの？
Oh, we're doing Tayousei?
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
我愛你 酔いが醒めない
Wo ai ni, I can't sober up
Oh I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh I need you, my love won't fade
お生憎様の慣れ果て殺して
Unfortunately, kill off the remnant
無問題 破滅してみて
No problem, try to be ruined
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対 お手お座りでハイ♡報酬
Strongly against, hand, sit, yes ♡ reward
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat stings
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Try to erase my loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も独彩して
Dominate both love and romance
僕を独占して
Monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよ
Let's keep kissing until we're addicted
そして Get get get on!
And Get get get on!
Get on chu!
Get get get on!
熱く とろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
My feelings overflow until they're hot and melting
たまらないでしょ
It's unbearable, right?
Get get get on! Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題 Get Get Get on chu!
Wo ai ni, no problem, Get Get Get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pong, Chi, Kan, the game is always...
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Tontinkan, if you ask me...
ちんぷんかんぷんだ 最後はロンでしょ？
Gibberish, in the end it's Ron, right?
もう何回？殺られればいい
How many more times? How many times must I be killed?
Oh One night 忘れられない
Oh One night, I can't forget
終わんないトキメキ恋愛予習
Never-ending heart-throb love practice
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat is prickling
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping
心臓ごと引きずり出してみせてよ
Drag my whole heart right out
ってよ
Show me now
きもちいい面倒くさいけど
It feels good, though it's a hassle
やっぱ照れくさいけど
It's embarrassing after all
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget until we die
いかれた魂はゾンビで溢れる
My broken soul is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You're in love with me
ときめく胸に繋がるロープを
The rope connected to my throbbing chest
引きなよ
Pull it in
Bet bet on! Bet bet on!
Bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの美しさが
The beauty that makes you go truly crazy
美しいでしょ
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on! Get get get on!
Get on chu!
せーの
One, two!
ポンチカン 終わんない
Ponchikan, never-ending
Get Get Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題
Wǒ ài nǐ, wú wèntí
Get Get Get on chu!
わぁー！
Wow!
やったー！うまくいったしんよ！
We did it! It went perfectly!
ありがとう！よかったー！
Thank you! That was great!
頑張ったねクロちゃん！
You did your best, Kuro-chan!
楽しかったー！ありがとう！
That was fun! Thank you!
えっと、ちょっとね、さよならする前に
Um, before we say goodbye...
お？
Oh?
えっと、一個お願いしてもいいですか？
Could I ask you for one favor?
一個だけだしん？
Just one favor?
一個だけじゃん！
Just one!
えっと、フワモコは魔界の番犬で
Um, FUWAMOCO are the guard dogs of the underworld...
「バウバウ」ってよく言ってるんですけど
And we often say "Bau Bau,"
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、フワモコのように
So Kuro-chan, could you look at the camera
かわいい「バウバウ」をしてもらえますか？
and do a cute "Bau Bau" like FUWAMOCO?
えぇー！できるかしんー！
Ehh! I wonder if I can do it!
行くしんよー！
Here I go!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
あはは！バウバウ！
Haha! Bau Bau!
それがベスト！
That's the best!
え、もう一回！もっとやって！
Wait, one more time! Do it more!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
かわいいかなー？
Was that cute?
実はもう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど
Actually, there's one more thing I want to do.
なに？
What is it?
さっきやりましたけど、フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって
We did it earlier, but FUWAMOCO has a self-introduction we always do.
できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
I'd love for the three of us to do it together!
あ、あれかわいかったからやりたいしん！
Oh, that was so cute, I want to do it too!
じゃあ、いきますよ！
Okay, here we go!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよー！
I'm not a Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
ババババー！フワワじゃないよ、クロちゃんだよー！
Ba-ba-ba-bau! I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Kuro-chan!
えぇー！クロちゃんじゃないよ、モココだよー！
Ehh! You're not Kuro-chan, I'm Mococo!
3人合わせて
Together, the three of us...
いやいやいやいや、バウバウ！
Iya-iya-iya-iya, Bau Bau!
なーにー！怒んないでー！どうしたの？
What? Don't get mad! What happened?
違う違う、クロちゃん！それじゃないから！
No, no, Kuro-chan! That wasn't it!
もう嘘とかつかないよね？
You won't tell any more lies, right?
つかないと...
If you do...
モココパンチしちゃうよ！
Mococo will punch you!
痛いー！救急車一台ー！
Ow! Someone call an ambulance!
いらないよ！もう嘘つかないで！
We don't need one! No more lies!
なんでプンプン怒るの、ちょっとー！
Why are you so mad? Geez!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて！
Calm down, calm down!
大丈夫、モコちゃん大丈夫！
It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay!
じゃあ、クロちゃんはこれからも、みんなをいっぱい笑顔にして
Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile
素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
and continue being a wonderful idol!
なしよ！
Yes, sir!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
じゃあ、モコちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね。
Moco-chan, let's high-five Kuro-chan and say goodbye.
おっけー。
Okay.
仲直り、仲直り、いい？
Let's make up, okay?
ハイタッチ！ハイタッチ！
High five! High five!
ハイタッチ！
High five!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ひどくない、もうちょっとー！なんしんのこれー！
That was mean! What was that all about?!
けど、フワモコちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございまーす！
But FUWAMOCO, a very Happy Birthday to you both!
わぁー！ありがとう！
Wow! Thank you!
おめでとうしんよー！バウバウ！
Happy birthday! Bau Bau!
キュンからのバッキューン！おめでとうハート！
From kyun to bakkyun! Happy birthday heart!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
花火だー！
Fireworks!
ペロの花火だー！わぁー、きれいー！
It's Pero fireworks! Wow, so pretty!
たまやー！
Tamaya!
かぎやー！バウバウ！
Kagiya! Bau Bau!
わぁー！
Wow!
すごーい！
Amazing!
わぁー、本当にきれい！
Wow, they're so beautiful!
空が本当にすごいことになってるけど
The sky has really gone crazy,
何が起こったのかよくわかんないよ！
but I'm not quite sure what happened!
色がホントすごすぎて分からなくなってきたかも！
The colors are so intense I might be losing it!
でも、まだもう一個すごく楽しみなことがあるんだよ！
But we still have one more very exciting thing to do!
まだまだ楽しみがあるよ！
There's still more fun to come!
わぁー！
Wow!
何かなー？何かなー？
I wonder what it is? What is it?
フワモコの1周年記念だよ！
It's FUWAMOCO's first anniversary!
We were able to release our very first original song,
"Wacha Wacha Party!" BAU BAU!
And then for our second anniversary, we were able to release "Lifetime Showtime,"
our original song that's been with us along this journey.
A very special song.
And you know, for FuwaMoco, singing and dancing
is something that means so much to us.
Yeah, music!
And Ruffians, you might have heard
that you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Yeah!
What do you think? Yeah!
Well, our announcement is...
Drumroll! OK, drumroll, yes!
Pupupupupupupupupupupupu...
DUN! A new original song!
新曲！新オリジナル曲！
A new song! A new original song!
And this song is extra special!
It's written by none other than the legendary
rock idol song composer Matsukuma Kenta-san,
who works with many famous idol groups we love,
also written music for the idol group that Kuro-chan produces,
MAMESHIBA NO TAIGUN-san!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, OK?
So get ready.
Ruffians, with this song, we'd like to express
our deepest feelings as Demon Dogs.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
Lyrics: 海野水玉 Music: 松隈ケンタ Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
Lyrics: Mizutama Umino Music: Kenta Matsukuma Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"Partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
We slip past the neon lights
バブルガムがはじけたら
When the bubblegum pops
let's go
最低な夜を潜って
Diving through the worst of nights
僕らは群れをなす
We form our pack
「あの頃よりもマシだね」
"It's better than those days, isn't it?"
my way
「不完全なんです」
"We are incomplete"
首輪をつけた
Putting on our collars
良い子なんかじゃもう
We're no longer good girls
イ。ヤ。
No more.
Ah!! DEMON'S RESIDENCE 噛みついていけ
Ah!! DEMON'S RESIDENCE, go and bite
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
気分はどうだい 泣いているのかい
How do you feel? Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs
I want to keep shouting, stray dogs
彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を
At the birds flying to the distance
見上げるだけかい それでいいのかい
Will you just look up? Is that enough for you?
燃えるなら ほら
If you're going to burn, look
青く
Burn blue
「説教なんかいらない」
"I don't need any lectures"
スプレー缶振って
Shake the spray can
イタズラ書きで彩る
Decorating with graffiti
runway
on the runway
愛情なんか coin toss
Love is just a coin toss
誰に bet するのか
Who are you betting on?
不確定要素ばかりね
Nothing but uncertain factors
lonely
二人でひとつと決めた
Decided we're two as one
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 満天の空
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, the star-filled sky
あの星がひどく不快で
Those stars are so unpleasant
勝利はどうだい 味がするのかい
How's the victory? Does it have a taste?
鎖を噛んで
Bite the chains
唸っていたいんだ stray dogs
I want to keep growling, stray dogs
僕ら宇宙さえも撃ち落として
We'll shoot down even the universe
見下ろす奈落 ビルは輝く
Looking down at the abyss, the buildings shine
LOL Now I am free!!
Woah woah woah...
孤独を分け合い食べた
We shared and ate our loneliness
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day
嗚呼 夜を睨んだ stray dogs そうだ
Ah, staring into the night, stray dogs, that's right
怪物（モンスター）は世界のほうさ
The monsters are the world itself
抜け出せるのかい 足は動くかい
Can you escape? Can your legs move?
走るなら今
If you're going to run, now's the time
DEMON'S RESIDENCE stray dogs 僕ら
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, stray dogs, we
この街を駆けて行け
Will run through this city
地獄の果てに 何が見えるかい
At the end of hell, what will you see?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs 僕ら
I want to keep shouting, stray dogs, we
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
君ならどうだい 共に駆けるかい？
How about you? Will you run with us?
夜明けが合図だ
Dawn is the signal
行こう
Let's go
Encore!
side by side
Bau bau!
Thank you for always being here for us, Ruffians!
Please listen to "side by side"!
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
Stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though, there's been rough times when nobody wanted us,
We kept going, and we kept dreaming!
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore,
Ruffians are together, we have smiles to protect!
Come on, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya nya nya nya...
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore, Ruffians!
That was "side by side"! Bau bau!
We're really happy to perform "side by side" for the first time live today!
Yeah! 初披露できてとっても嬉しいです！
Yeah! I'm so happy we got to perform it for the first time!
"side by side" is a song made by Alobahn-san, but also between FuwaMoco!
Yeah, and us!
I know, we know it's a song that you love a lot,
but we also do because it's very special to us since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about!
Nekopara!
Nekopara! Bau bau!
And with this song, our dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
Yeah! そう、この曲でフワモコの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
Yeah! That's right, with this song, FuwaMoco's dream of singing a bishojo game theme song has come true!
Yeah, it came true! Thank you!
Thank you!
ありがとう！
And thank you so much for joining us for our special day again this year!
It's been a dream with you!
And you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here
and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you!
Thank you!
This next song...
...is our last song!
But like all of them, it's a very special one.
You know FUWAMOCO...
...is Demon Guard Dogs!
We're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that.
Protect your smile!
Yeah!
Do our best as idols!
And just as our fluffy and fuzzy souls, too.
We'll continue to be here for
thousands and thousands of demon dog years.
All while remembering that, you know,
every day isn't given.
Yeah!
We don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down,
we hope that you'll remember...
...that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We'll cheer you on, Ruffians!
So please listen closely to the lyrics
of our last song for today.
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように　ずっと
I hope you'll keep on smiling forever.
Lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for
spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things are rough...
...and know we'll be here!
This last song is for you, Wishful☆Garnet!
過去を振り返ると
When I look back at the past,
思い出すガーネットの空
I remember the Garnet sky.
溢れてく　光
The light overflows.
この瞳に映し出されたあの日は
That day reflected in these eyes
美しく　揺れる
sways beautifully.
What do you think?
赤く滲んだ空に
In the sky tinged with red,
願いました　どうかこの願い　届けてください
I made a wish. Please, let this wish reach you.
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll keep on smiling.
離れ離れになっても　前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を　わたしが壊してあげる
The chains that bind you, I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと　いつでもそばにいるから
Keep moving forward without losing,
because I'll always be by your side.
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when I felt down or lost my confidence,
目の前にいてくれる
you were right there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度となく　救われた
I've been saved by your smile time and time again.
だから
That's why,
So I love you
挫けそうになったら　手を伸ばして
If you feel like giving up, just reach out your hand.
まだ知らない明日　一緒に見つけよう
Let's find the unknown tomorrow together.
明日も　明後日も　あなたを照らしていたい
Tomorrow, and the day after too, I want to keep shining on you.
泣きそうになった時は　こっち向いてほしい
When you feel like crying, please look my way.
世界でひとりのぼっち　そんな風に思わないで
Don't ever think that you're alone in the world.
愛してくれる人はきっと　いつもあなたを想ってる
There's surely someone who loves you,
and is always thinking of you.
Lala...
願いました　どうかこの願い　届けてください
I made a wish. Please, let this wish reach you.
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll keep on smiling.
離れ離れになっても　前を向けますように
Even if we are far apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を　わたしが壊してあげる
The chains that bind you, I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Keep moving forward without losing,
輝く空へ
to the shining sky.
明日も　明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll keep on smiling.
離れ離れに
Even if we are separated
なっても前を
and far apart,
向けますように
I hope you can keep looking forward.
あなたを
The chains
縛る鎖を
that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで
Don't lose anymore,
進むこと
keep moving forward.
いつでもそばに
Always by your side,
あなたのそばに
right next to you,
わたしはいつもいるから
I will always be there for you.
La la la...
Oh yeah...
Yeah, yeah...
La la la...
Bau bau!
Thank you so much for viewing!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
Bau bau!
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
We'll be waiting for you at the members-only encore live!